[
    {
        "username": "asdgasg",
        "qid": 1,
        "question": "Do you smoke?",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "username": "asdgasg",
        "qid": 2,
        "question": "Do you drink more than three times a week?",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "username": "asdgasg",
        "qid": 3,
        "question": "How many roommates do you prefer",
        "answer": "3 or more"
    },
    {
        "username": "asdgasg",
        "qid": 4,
        "question": "Which do you do more?",
        "answer": "Eat out"
    },
    {
        "username": "asdgasg",
        "qid": 5,
        "question": "Will you share household supplies (toiletries, cleaning supplies, etc.)",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "username": "asdgasg",
        "qid": 6,
        "question": "Are you a part or full-time student?",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "username": "asdgasg",
        "qid": 7,
        "question": "Do you own a car?",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "username": "asgag",
        "qid": 1,
        "question": "Do you smoke?",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "username": "asgag",
        "qid": 2,
        "question": "Do you drink more than three times a week?",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "username": "asgag",
        "qid": 3,
        "question": "How many roommates do you prefer",
        "answer": "2"
    },
    {
        "username": "asgag",
        "qid": 4,
        "question": "Which do you do more?",
        "answer": "Eat out"
    },
    {
        "username": "asgag",
        "qid": 5,
        "question": "Will you share household supplies (toiletries, cleaning supplies, etc.)",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "username": "asgag",
        "qid": 6,
        "question": "Are you a part or full-time student?",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "username": "asgag",
        "qid": 7,
        "question": "Do you own a car?",
        "answer": "No"
    }
]